Guys
I don't know why everyone goes so nuts. I mean summer and 30 diamond. Can you not show your
Thank you those pictures and stuff. Hey, what's up, Jamie?
Who's getting a little bit intense?
You know what I'm okay. Hey, what's up shepherd? Hey summer. Yeah, I don't want you guys to have a
You might have to be fighting it or but I know I know you guys can you know both ships photos and stuff like this
Just talking and talking to stuff just talk
Everything's okay guys
Thank you, I didn't start anything I was
You know, let's let's not go into like
You're old and you're fucking a man bitch. I don't you're not saying nothing original to me
You're learning how to be original, like if you want to, if you want to be original, like okay, thank you for being original, you know what I'm saying, thank you for being original, thank you for being original, now you're being original.
Your store bought, your appeal bought bitch, remember that, everything on you is fake.
I know, I don't take pills, I don't pop pills, I do.
Yeah, yeah, you take shots bitch.
I don't pop pills, I do.
You take pills, you take, you take, I don't take pills bitch, you take pills.
And you literally pop Adderall, you pop Danette, you literally pop Danette.
I don't take any of that.
Let's take a drug test right now, bitch, and let's see who takes what because I'm clean all the weed, bitch
No, you're on drugs
Try again, bitch. Try again. You want to pass the drug test?
Any drug test you want any time, bitch? Oh, I will
Okay, we'll do it. We'll do a drug test together. Let's meet up. Let's hang out. Let's hang out. Meet up
Yeah, let's hang out. Let's meet up. Let's meet up. Let's meet up
I'm the get that key. Come on. I'll meet up with you. I'll meet up with you before I leave california
I'll meet up with you. I'm not in california
Okay, I'll visit you before I go to my other state that I'm going to next night. I'm in Kentucky. Let me know when you're here
Okay, I'll visit you in Kentucky
Yeah, let's go to Kentucky. I'm moving away flirty. We'll have a ball. I
Actually would hang out with you somewhere like I'm not even playing with you. I would hang out with you, too
It's the Nando bullshit. This is a senseless drama that shouldn't be going on between us. You're the one starting a drama
What
I don't have control of Regine, Regine says to you it's not my personal thing, you are not tagged in nothing, I deleted you from the tag.
And you would still talk and shit. You're not tag no more
I'm not I'm not deleting those messages for what what has it benefited you I don't care
You're gonna you're gonna reap what you sow I could promise you that one these days
Keep wishing me death
No
He wished me death he wished me
I'll let you know when I wish you death. I wish me death
Okay, one second, let me show him my dick one second. Oh, no, no, okay
There you go. Oh my god. I
Don't know what we're looking. Okay. There you go. There you go, Chris. You put the can in our fucking shit
There you go, baby
Not that big baby. Oh, it's very big baby. It's very bad. Oh, it's very big. Oh, I bet. Oh, you want to suck it and find out
No, I'm good, bitch. I'm sorry. I like black. I like black big first of all. I'm here, too
I like I like you. I only suck my husband's dick. Oh, I liked it, too. Well, good
Great. Have fun with that
What are you doing? Are you crazy? Oh, I'm positive. I'm positive. I'm sure I'm maybe I'll trick him. Maybe I'll trick him
Try if you think you can
Don't worry
Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to you. Give it to
Okay, you just got both you guys a city like what I never knew is to run and chase after no fucking body. I understand that
Go for it. Oh my god, go for it. I love that flabby knock-needed ass
Start showing updated photos. You can find my photos on Twitter. This is two months ago, bitch
Yeah, two months ago show updated ones. Yeah, I don't look for your shit. I found this on somebody screens
Okay, I
Don't go look for your shit. You don't matter that much bitch. I obviously do for you to be having my photos in your computer
I
Have that video I'll keep showing as long as she's showing my shit psyche. I'm gonna show it. So
Every time when she shows my shit and there she went again important bomb do psyche because my boss are showing them that photo
There she goes poor bombing you because Christina me are kissing
She showed a picture of that and I'll do it every time as long as you allow her to do that
Well, I did it. I showed a photo of you guys kissing after you showed my balls just now
No, you had the first at first. I had the ass picture not this one. I switched this to that one holler
I literally know I didn't
I'll do it. I don't give a fuck. He don't care. I don't give a fuck